(Sheldon:)the severing of which would
cause me any discomfort.
(Sheldon:)The relationship simply
outlived its utility,
(Sheldon:)and I'm continuing on
with my life as before.
(Penny:)Okay. Good.
(Sheldon:)Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm off to buy a pussycat.
(Leonard:)I gotta tell you guys,
(Leonard:)I'm a little worried about Sheldon.
(Howard:)We're all a little
worried about Sheldon.
(Leonard:)No, I mean since the
Shamy hit a reef.
(Howard:)Oh, I thought you were just
making a generalization:
"You know,
I'm worried about Sheldon
"someday setting off a
low-yield nuclear device
(Howard:)because the cafeteria
ran out of lime Jell-O."
What does "hit a reef" mean?
(Leonard:)Uh, went splitsville.
(Raj:)Pardon?
(Leonard:)Turned to boom-boom.
(Sheldon:)Ah.
(Leonard:)I think Sheldon really misses Amy.
You should lend him your copy of
Bombay Badonkadonks.
(Leonard:)He got a cat to keep him company.
(Raj:)You're kidding.
He takes it everywhere:
(Leonard:)to bed, to the bathroom.
(Raj:)He takes the kitty to the potty?
(Howard:)I thought we discussed the P-word.